My Bey, why are they
waiting? Where are they?
They won't attack.
What's their intention, Osman Bey?
They want to slow us down.
Slow us down.
There are horses deep in the forest.
They are shooting from there.
It's obvious from the speed of the arrows.
They are not crowded.
They are trying to make
themselves look crowded.
Who are they my Bey?
Orhan is in danger.
We need to go quickly!
Come on
Come on alps!
What should we do my Bey?
We won't stop.
It looks like Osman
realized what's going on.
Osman will not make
it in time for his son.
Come on.
Stall them as long as you can.
As you command my Bey.
Come on!
Orhan, go.
Go, Orhan, save yourself.
No, if I do that...
..I will die!
Enough!
First she will die..
...then you will die!
Holofira! You are okay right?
I am okay.
But you are wounded.
You are..
...my remedy.
This way!
This forest will be your grave!
Damn dastard.
He will get his turn, but not now.
Come on Holofira.
Where is Orhan?
We turned their wedding
into a nightmare, my Bey.
My shahzade kidnapped Holofira Hatun.
Lucas must have
surrounded the whole forest.
They can't get out.
Where are they?
They went North, my Bey.
You left them alone?
Shahzade Orhan was wounded.
We lured the soldiers to open their path.
What?
We had to, my Bey.
What are we going to do now, father?
He is wounded, huh?
It's hard for them to escape.
We will ride North!
Come.
This way, come on.
Where did they go?
This way!
Come on!
Orhan.
They went over here.
Bring the horses now!
Orhan.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm okay Holofira.
Your wound is too deep.
How will we leave here?
We will.
We will leave, Lord's daughter.
We won't surrender.
We'll go to our home.
We'll go back to our tents, if Allah permits.
I know.
In the name of Allah.
I asked you a question, Lord's daughter.
Do you remember?
I want an answer.
Will you be my partner,
...join me in my dreams...
..and be my confidant?
Orhan.
Orhan. They're coming!
Go over there.
Watch my signal.
Now!
Orhan!
I'll crush you..
...under my horse, without using a sword.
I'll cut off your head..
...and bring peace to
this world. Count on it!
Come here.
Osman and his men are coming.
This won't end here.
We'll meet again.
Whenever you want Arcadeus.
What?
Let's get married.
We'll finally unite.
We will.
So, now you're telling me...
...you accept it?
And you accept my proposal is that so?
Allah.
Orhan!
My bey. Brother.
Thank Allah you're okay.
Son you're okay right?
Just a small wound, my bey.
But that's like an accessory for an alp.
Girl, are you okay?
I'm okay, thank you.
Good.
My bey.
I did this without asking your permission.
Please forgive me.
But...
Look here.
What are you saying?
Of course not.
If I was in your place...
..I would do the same.
Holofira can be considered my daughter.
My bey.
If it's okay with you too...
...I want her..
...to be both your daughter...
...and your daughter in law.
Osman Bey.
You always viewed me as your daughter.
And I always viewed you as my father too.
I wish to be your
daughter in law too, now.
..you say so..
It's okay with me too.
We should not stand
against those in love...
...but by their side.
Thank you my bey.
Then..
...let's go back to our
tribe and hold a big feast.
May your happiness
be everlasting, brother.
Thank you brother.
By the way, my bey...
...we stopped Karesi Bey from having fun.
He was there too.
Are you telling me that he was there too?
Orhan.
How dare you...
...kidnap a Byzantine aristocrat
from a Byzantine wedding?
How dare you?
I'm going to destroy you with your father.
Order us and we'll turn
their lands into ruins.
No Hristo, our pawns will do that for us.
What is your plan, commander?
We're going to make the Byzantine
people under Osman's rule riot.
But for that we need a spark.
Commander Lucas, thank God.
Father.
I'm so embarrassed.
After what Orhan made you go
through you must be so scared.
Such a low, dishonorable attack.
Where were you? Did anyone see you?
After the attack I hid in
my own house, commander.
No one saw me.
I would've loved to confess
in front of you one last time.
But...
...unfortunately...
...your life is not long enough for that.
That's the spark we were looking for, Hristo.
Take him away.
Send word to Arcadeus.
They'll have a small
similarity with the Father.
-Welcome.
-Welcome Osman Bey.
-Welcome back my bey.
-Welcome back.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-Welcome.
-Welcome back.
Welcome, Osman Bey!
Welcome, my Bey!
Welcome all!
Thank Allah. They've
returned safe and sound.
Welcome, my Bey!
Welcome!
-Father.
-Daughter.
Mother.
I've kept my promise and
brought your bride here.
I knew it. My Orhan
always keeps his promises.
Holofira.
Brother.
My sister.
-Welcome. Thank Allah.
-Mother.
May you always be happy, brother.
If Allah permits.
Welcome home, daughter.
Thank you.
Start preparations.
Let's have a great wedding.
Send words to the Beys.
But above all to Karasi Bey.
Because he likes celebrations
that much, let him see our wedding.
Let him come and see
how great our wedding is!
As you command, my Bey.
Beys.
I'll be waiting for you in my presence.
They won't even wait forty days after
our child's death, huh Alaaddin Bey?
Hey everyone!
The warriors of Holy Rome.
The forgiver of our sins..
..the hand of God on earth..
...our priest, has been slain!
-How can this be?
-How?
-How could they do this?
-Curse them!
The one, who killed our holy priest...
...the one, who insulted our holiness...
...is Orhan Bey!
Of course, he got the order
from his father, Osman Bey!
They killed the priest in order to
capture my bride at my wedding!
This is not only a loss.
This is an awakening!
Our enemies want to shake
our faith and destroy us...
...by targeting the servants of God!
Wake up!
-Tyrants!
Don't you think the time has come
for us to take revenge on the Turks?
It has!
-For Holy Rome!
-For our religion!
-For revenge!
Lukas and Karasi Bey.
They thought they could beat us when
they combined the sides of the water.
Blindness, Osman Bey.
They are in blindness.
But today, the fire
going through the skies...
...must have destroyed their
endurance and courage, for sure!
No.
The real headlessness is
when you underestimate your enemy...
...and lower your guard
as you think your enemy is incapable.
Do you think they will be
allies from now on, Osman Bey?
If I know Karasi Bey, he has no
business with the heathens but trading.
They've already become allies,
Begum Hatun, don't you see it?
The grudge they had against
us made them come together.
We heard that Karasi Bey
even went to their celebration.
From now on, their alliance is one
the most dangerous things we could face.
We will be cautious. We
will know of their every step.
You may leave.
Orhan.
Yes my Bey.
Prepare your best alp.
He will sneak into the infidels.
He will be Lucas' shadow.
We will know of every step Lucas takes.
As you command my Bey.
How could you forget so quickly?
How can you hold a wedding feast...
...as if nothing happened?
How can you accept Holofira?
But I won't forget.
I'll not forget, my baby.
Gonca.
I brought you sherbet.
You aren't eating anything.
At least drink this.
Ulgen.
Are you mocking me!?
Did you bring me the sherbet
you prepared for the feast?
I just wanted you to...
Gonca, are you okay?
Gonca.
Alaeddin, I am not okay!
As long as Holofira is
here, I won't be okay!
Gonca.
You know the best...
...about Holofira and my brother's
love, and the tests they went through.
After I lost my child..
...I forgot all I knew, Alaeddin!
Why don't you understand?
I feel hurt whenever I see her!
What should I do?
I know what we should do.
We should leave, Alaeddin.
If you love me..
...if you want my tears to stop...
...we should leave.
Just you and me.
Thank Allah we..
...brought Holofira back safe and sound.
Thank Allah my Bey.
Thank Allah.
So, Bala.
Where are Alaeddin and Gonca?
Gonca is not feeling well.
I didn't want Alaeddin to leave her alone.
You thought well.
We shouldn't leave her alone.
She is going through a lot.
But don't worry. From now on..
..we will overcome all the troubles.
If Allah permits.
So, my Bey.
We got the good news.
We are going to hold our wedding feast.
We are going to hold a
wedding feast my Bey.
We are, yes.
You know, before that...
Now...
...I need to give a speech.
And I have been waiting for
you to speak what's on your mind.
Then..
...there is no need to keep this going.
With the order of Allah and
the word of the prophet...
...I ask Holofira's hand in
marriage for my son Orhan.
You can't do it like that.
How should I do it?
We should think about it first.
Let's think.
...will your son take care of my girl?
What?
Mother.
Don't.
You know my brother.
Wait up. Wait.
Bala. Don't.
Sweetheart. My dear wife.
It's time to unite these lovers.
Let's not make them wait.
No.
I used to be on the groom's side.
Now I side with her.
I'll ask my girl first.
Sweet girl!
What do you think?
Say it Holofira.
Come on my girl. Speak.
I don't know.
Do as you wish mother Bala.
Don't do this my girl. Don't. Don't.
This is bad.
My Bey. We saved her from the Byzantines.
But we can't save her from mother Bala.
It's bad. She won't do it.
Of course.
Marrying a girl requires a lot of hard work!
How many times did you ask
my father if we could marry, Osman Bey?
Did you forget?
Mother Bala..
...knows I've been in love
with Holofira since I met her.
Yes.
Right, mother?
Yes. I know.
You know.
Yes.
Then..
...200 goats.
What?
1000 gold coins.
1000?
10...
20 camels.
20 camels?
We have to, my Bey.
It's 30 now.
Bala.
My Bey. If you wait longer it'll be more.
I accept.
Good.
If they love each other...
...and if they wish to unite...
...we must build a home for them.
That's it.
Hold on. Hold on.
I accept.
That's it.
Good.
Thank Allah.
What is this?
What is that sound?
What are you doing here?
Why are you here? Go back!
Go back! Go away!
Leave!
Just you and two of your men.
The rest will stay.
Take their swords.
Osman!
You may win for now..
...but it won't last long.
The wounds we caused made
you come all this way, I see.
Commander.
I'd say that you heard
about our wedding feast...
...which is in two days but...
...it's not the right time.
Besides we didn't invite you either.
...came here to take
Holofira where she belongs.
You come to my tribe.
You stand in front of me...
...and ask for my daughter in law huh?
Is that so?
You, Osman Bey...
...ruined my bridge.
Your son Orhan came
into my lands with his men...
...and ruined the wedding.
A Byzantine royalty...
He kidnapped Arcedeus's bride-to-be.
I won't let this go.
Is that so?
What will you do?
Either I'll take Holofira and leave...
Or?
Or it will cost you a lot.
Look at me.
That bridge which you
tried to build with Karesi...
Do you remember the fire there?
If you try to make me pay a price...
...don't you dare forget those fires.
Because..
..with every move you make..
...the only thing you'll see...
..will be that fire.
I'm already where I belong.
Leave me alone.
You're going to regret this Holofira.
You too.
Here is the field.
Here is the man.
Come on. Let us see you too.
She brought trouble...
...alongside herself.
Kayi Tents
-Come on. Fill the cups.
-Come on.
One for Saruca.
-You can drink it come on.
-Write it down.
-Come on. Drink it.
-One for me too.
-Come on.
Write one down for Yusuf.
Come on be quick.
-Come on. Write it down.
-One for Saruca. Come on Yusuf.
Come on brother Yusuf,
don't let him take the lead.
Don't give up, brother!
Again!
Come on! Come on now!
He won't be able to drink this!
Come on, don't give up
now, brother! Don't give up!
Don't give up, come on!
Boran Bey, it's hitting me
hard, Boran Bey! I won't stop!
Belly on the horse, strength with the man!
Look he'll give up! Come on!
Come on!
The one burning fast, goes
out early, Boran brother.
Brothers, bring some water.
It's a draw.
It will be repeated!
Mother! Mother! Mother!
You are being called.
In Karacahisar, Yenisher and
Sogut, with the order of Lukas...
...you've gotten into the
Greeks, who live in the
fake heaven of Osman
and won their hearts.
Now, it's time to bring
rebellion, grudge...
...and hatred into those hearts!
They'll riot for the
revenge of their priest!
Karacahisar, Yenisehir and Sogut...
...will be destroyed with
the rebellion of the Greeks!
Now, go and start the war.
As you command!
This armed angry crowd
will be your end, Osman.
Sergeant Aykut, they've been
gathering in this house since morning.
Then, there is something wrong.
No one will reveal himself. Send
words to the tribe immediately!
As you command, my Bey.
We've heard you are a
talented stableman, Irbay.
Though our horses in good hands,
our intention is that they never reach that.
As we all know, your
intellect and strength
is much better than
a common stableman.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-It's alright.
And you should know that we
see you more than a stableman.
I'm ready for any order.
But in this road, you
could be a martyr or ghazi.
There are many difficulties,
you should know that.
I'm ready to die for Osman Bey
and you, my Shehzade and my state
May you live long. Then, your duty is...
...going to Lukas as a spy.
We need to know what
he is eating, where he
is going, in short,
everything about him.
As you command, my Bey.
But...
...my daughter, my dear, my Ayse.
Protect her, my Bey.
Don't worry. Now...
Now, listen to me carefully, Ilbay.
Yusuf.
What's wrong?
I beat Sarica in the pekmez war.
When I got the last glass,
he was already on the ground.
Praise be, praise be.
Since when courage is
measured by pekmez jars?
In the name of Allah.
Yusuf, instead of doing
unnecessary things like this...
...try to win Fatma Hatun's heart.
Sister.
You ask me to win Fatma Hatun's heart.
And you also keep fighting Bala Hatun.
Why is that?
Since when do you question my decisions?
I know what to do.
How can I win her heart when
you make her mother angry at us?
Tell me that.
It's my duty to put
people in their places...
...and it's your duty to win...
...her heart.
Use your head.
Okay.
Mother!
I am dying mother!
You can't die from eating pekmez.
It hurts, mother!
Let me get you some water.
Mother!
Drink this.
Don't give me more pekmez, mother!
It's water! Drink it!
Mother!
Get up! Get up!
Get up! Stand straight.
You need to stand
straight in front of a Hatun.
Hey. Stop it.
Stop it. Stand up.
Stand tall and strong.
Then..
...take a glance and touch your mustache.
Sarica.
Do it like your father.
I don't have a mustache mother.
Have a clean voice.
Peace be with you Hatun.
Just tell her, "Say your name."
Say it.
I know her name mother. It's Fatma.
Fatma, mother.
Then...
...read her a poem by the master Yunus.
Hear my words, oh my friends.
Love is a valuable thing.
You can't name a price for it.
Love is greater thing.
Hey.
Hold on Bayhan Bey.
You never told me a poem.
Never stroke your mustache.
Hatun...WelL
Did you read poems to other
Hatuns and touch your mustache?
I want to die! I want to die! Allah!
Allah!
Hatun! My sweetheart.
Look at your tiny body.
Tiny body?
Allah! I'm too old to be cheated on.
Father.
You have to stand up straight
in front of women, father.
Stand tall, father.
Allah..
Like this father.
Allah...Bayhan what are you doing?
Allah, look at what has happened to me.
Osman Bey is coming, be ready.
Come on.
Where did they come from my bey?
What are they doing here?
Lucas must've found out about us.
They're out of arrows, my bey.
Come on alps.
Alps.
Hit the chests of the infidels.
Allah is the greatest!
That dog called Lucas!
He is attacking us like a rabid dog!
That demon!
He will keep attacking us.
But we...
...we will always be cautious.
That's why, we will...
...increase security in the
cities, tribes and borders.
That dastard..
...will not be able to breathe!
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Send word to Gencer Bey.
We will inspect the borders.
He should arrive as soon as possible.
As you command my Bey.
You are always alone, Karesi Bey.
You are standing alone.
We are the soldiers of the sea.
Those who live on the seas
are used to being lonely.
Now tell me, what's the reason...
...for your visit?
I have a new plan against Osman.
That will destroy him...
...completely.
I am listening.
Until today, all the beylics
made wrong moves.
They tried to make Osman
pledge loyalty by forcing him.
But he is a man who is not afraid of death.
You can't make him kneel by fighting.
But..
...if you cut his arms,
he will fall slowly.
Cut them!
Cut them then!
Do it! what are you waiting for?
I will cut them, Karesi Bey.
But with you.
Together with you.
While the Greek rebellion, we
will start in Osman's lands spread...
...it will provoke Turkish people as well.
The civil war in his lands..
..will weaken him.
You...
...will take his Beys.
And I will take Karadin castle back.
Great!
A great...
...plan.
I will support you with
all my power Lucas.
Tell me what to do.
Osman will increase
security in my borders.
But he doesn't suspect you.
What I want from you is...
...that while I am moving
my army to Karadin castle...
...I will use your lands secretly.
We are in this together.
Your army can use my lands freely.
Karesi Bey, you know, when you
fall in these lands, you get swallowed.
But if you and I stand together...
...no one can defeat us.
No one can!
My dear.
Stop sulking, okay?
But you are leaving me behind.
My duty is important.
And I am not leaving you behind.
How could I do that?
Look...
...carry you right in my heart.
Then return swiftly, father.
I will, my girl.
I will.
Mekece Border
Take a look.
Alps!
Take a look at them.
Enjoy your meal.
Gencer Bey.
Is this good?
Osman Bey.
Go! Go! Go!
Osman Bey. Forgive me.
We didn't know.
You didn't know?
You didn't?
Did you hear Gencer bey?
They didn't know.
They didn't know we'd be here.
My Bey.
If you did, you wouldn't light a
fire and hunt and hang out here?
Right?
If you knew we'd be here..
...you'd do your duty fully.
Right?
Those who fail to complete duty...
...can't protect their
Hatun or their children.
They can't!
Gencer Bey.
What is a watch?
Boran!
My Bey.
What is a watch?
Taking a watch means honor.
An Alp's grace.
An Alp's honor.
His grace!
One will stay awake unlike the rest.
One will stay hungry when others are full.
Soldiers need to protect the people...
..and our state.
But no.
You won't protect them.
Now get out of here.
Gencer Bey.
Don't...
...be fooled ever again.
All of us will protect
the borders together.
As you wish my Bey.
The wedding will happen soon.
All of you know what to do.
Don't make me say it again.
Is that new honey?
It tastes good.
What is it?
Welcome Hazal Hatun.
Why are you here?
I'm here to help Ulgen.
No need. No need but thank you.
Are those fruits?
Wait hold on.
Is it good?
It's good sister. It is.
Do you have to eat all
of it to know it's good?
Take it away before they're done.
It's all okay if you're full,
don't help us anymore.
I'll handle it.
She's worse than Cerkutay.
Mother.
Yes? What?
I want my wedding feast
preparations to be like this too.
Is that so? What else?
Ayse, no one would marry you.
You're done now Ghazi.
Shame.
You can't watch me Ayse.
I'll catch you.
You can't.
Mother Bala.
You are troubling
yourself too much for us.
What are you saying girl?
We're preparing for our son
and daughter's wedding feast.
Bala Hatun.
The gems and fabric we asked
for the wedding dress have arrived.
They're all so shiny.
Good.
Let me see.
Very nice.
Holofira, girl...
...if you want another fabric,
tell me and we'll get them.
They're all so pretty.
Gonca Hatun.
Come.
Hazal Hatun what are you doing?
Wait.
Bala Hatun bought such pretty
fabrics, she's clearly very generous.
She is. She is Hazal Hatun.
Praise be, my mother
has always been like that.
But we have to be careful.
Trouble has arrived here.
Mother Bala, if you allow me...
...I want to speak with Gonca.
As you wish girl.
But she's in so much
pain, I understand her.
It's very fresh too.
Please don't forget that okay?
Don't worry.
Kismet, sisters...
...bring the fabrics to
Holofira's tent. Go on.
My bey.
There's word from Sogut.
What is it?
Is it something bad?
The Greeks, they're
gathering secretly in a house.
What are they gathering for?
They are the powerful Greeks
that are under our rule, my bey.
We don't know why they're gathering.
But Sergeant Aykurt is suspicious of them.
Something is clearly up.
Let's go and see them there.
Let's see why they gathered.
Let them prepare my horse.
As you wish my bey.
Orhan Bey.
I wish to come with you.
If we don't help now then when will we?
I wish to participate, Orhan Bey.
Okay. Come on then.
Gonca Hatun.
You don't see well.
Is there something I can do for you?
No I'm okay.
I'll be okay.
Thank you Begum Hatun.
Gonca.
Can we talk a bit?
Holofira, leave.
I have nothing to talk with you.
Gonca please don't do this.
I didn't know.
I swear I didn't know
that she was the traitor.
It's best that I leave you alone.
It's clearly a family matter.
No.
Stay, Begum Hatun.
Everyone knows what has happened.
Hear what she has to say too.
What could happen?
Holofira.
You caused the death of my child.
Look.
They're preparing a wedding.
Please, don't talk like this.
You are my sister.
-And when I heard that...
-What?
When you heard that, what did you do?
Did you get upset so much,
Holofira? Tell me! You got upset?
What you said is true. You were my sister.
You were my closest sister.
You made me sit at the
table with the killer of my child.
For this, my pain never goes away.
My hatred never goes away.
When I see you, my pain
increases, don't you see it, Holofira?
Kill me, then. Stop your pain.
If you were my enemy...
..I wouldn't wait a
second and take your life.
But you were my sister, Holofira!
You were my closest sister!
I didn't only bury my child that day...
..I also buried you.
Never forget this.
Look at that black widow!
So, you've made your choice!
Holofira Hatun, my daughter!
Don't be sad, come on.
You did nothing wrong.
I'm not upset for myself, Hazal Hatun.
Gonca is in great pain.
That's why I'm upset.
She is in pain but she also
ruins your most happy day.
That's wrong.
Come on, don't be sad.
The tailors are waiting for you.
BAYHAN BEY BORDER LINE
We'll go on foot.
Bayhan Bey is waiting for us. Let's
see what's going on in his borders
Come on, Alps!
Stop!
Who are you?
Where are you going?
Get out of the way.
You can't beat us.
Alps!
Now, I can beat you.
I'm asking one last time! Who are you?
Alps!
This is Bayhan Bey!
Attention, whom you see is Osman Bey!
May you live long.
May you live long, warriors.
We need such warriors, who
takes responsibility on their duty.
May you live long.
We need to send these
bold warriors across our lands.
-Bayhan Bey -My Bey.
May you live long, too.
You trained them well. They
keep their duties perfectly.
We are always on our duty, my Bey.
Thank you.
Now, Karadin is next.
Let's inspect...
...Begum Hatun's borders.
I wish I had not given you that halwa.
I haven't been able
to sleep since that day.
You are not at fault, Begum Hatun.
Those who are at fault are obvious.
But no one can see them.
They don't want to see them.
The one who brought the traitor into
the tribe is just as guilty as the traitor.
Seeing Holofira is
reminding you of bad things.
And they are holding a wedding.
Well..
..it hurts me.
What strangers understand...
...is not understood by my beloved ones.
Neither my mother, nor my husband...
..can see the state I am in.
They can't choose.
Orhan Bey is behind Holofira after all.
It looks like...
...I have nothing but my
baby's grave in his tribe.
No.
Gonca.
Don't be like this.
You are powerful.
But you are not alone.
I am with you.
Think of me as your sister.
No matter what you need, no
matter whom you are against...
...know that I'll always support you.
Gonca.
Mother.
I wanted to come to
see if you are doing okay.
I am okay, mother.
I didn't know you were here, Begum Hatun.
I wanted to have a chat with Gonca Hatun.
You thought well.
But...
..now Gonca needs to rest.
We should talk a little, huh?
People!
Repair and wash everything!
Shine everything!
Come with me. Come on!
At the seat of every Bey, there will be...
...pieces from their beylics.
For example, in Karesi Bey's seat...
...there will be a...
...big sea shell.
Come on!
Don't place the banners there!
Begum Hatun.
You must be feeling a
guilty conscience as you...
...are treating Gonca kindly.
There is no ill intentions
behind it, right?
I didn't want her to feel alone.
Gonca is my daughter, Begum Hatun.
So, she is not alone!
She is no different than
Alaeddin, Orhan and Fatma...
...in my eyes.
Just like Holofira.
She is going through hard times.
She is, but...
...if anyone tries to take advantage
of that and poison her mind...
...against her family and beloved ones...
...they will pay heavily for it!
I just wanted to console her.
Thanks.
Thanks, but...
...like I said before.
Just focus on your duty.
Begum Hatun.
Prepare the horses. We'll head out soon.
Bala Hatun.
I'll always be on top of my duty.
I'd never disappoint Osman Bey.
I wish for that to be true Begum Hatun.
It happened once.
I wouldn't want you to mess it all up..
...once again.
They gathered here last night Shehzade.
Why did they gather here Aykurt?
Did you find out?
I asked around but..
...I haven't heard anything.
The Greek people Osman Bey protects...
...gathered together at night.
And no one knows about it?
Something's off.
Shehzade.
Let's question them.
-No.
The water's muddy.
We need the water to be
clear to find out what's wrong.
But...
..let's show them we're on to them.
When the swords get to innocent Greeks...
..it'll turn them into an angry army.
Your men will be among the Greeks.
They'll cause chaos.
Good.
Soon, the fire of
hell will start in Sogut.
Open up!
Break it.
Orhan Bey.
Merchant Marco.
What is it?
Why are you late?
Is there a problem?
Forgive me Orhan Bey.
I was busy. I didn't know about it.
It's okay.
Merchant Marco.
Yesterday Alps let a criminal get away.
They saw Greek merchants here
when they left to look for him.
I wanted to ask you myself.
Are the Greek merchants in trouble?
Everyone prays for Osman Bey, Orhan Bey.
We gathered together to help the orphans.
To show your good faith...
...you gather aid from everyone.
Okay.
Thank you.
We're still looking for
the criminal on the run.
All the houses will be searched.
Can we come in?
Alps need to take a look.
Come in.
Aykurt.
Shut the door.
They're for innocent orphans.
Shehzade. There's no criminal inside.
Merchant Marco.
I'll send word to the
masters to help your charity.
Thank you Orhan Bey.
Thank you Merchant Marco.
Thank you.
Aykurt.
There's nothing suspicious inside, Shehzade.
What?
Was he honest?
It seems so.
They're doing charity to show good will.
But no one knows about it.
Aykurt.
Tell the alps to keep
their eyes on this house.
Something else is going on in there.
Stop.
I'm coming from Nikea.
The Lord of Nikea has
send these horses for...
...commander Lucas' powerful soldiers.
Show me your papers.
When you enter Bursa they
will definitely ask for your papers.
Search the person
responsible for the horses well.
We were waiting for you, you may enter.
-Welcome Osman Bey.
-Welcome my bey.
-Welcome bey.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
What is it Begum Hatun?
We've been going around for a while...
...but...
...we didn't see anyone but women.
Neither a guard or a
man that can use a sword.
Is this how you guard this place?
The Sisters!
There.
This is how I'm guarding
the grounds, Osman Bey.
So you make them these
clothes and do their jobs...
Alright.
You thought well, Begum Hatun.
We'll always follow you
on the path you opened up for us...
...with our wits
and swords, Osman Bey.
We started it all risking our lives...
...there's no going back now.
Thank you. Live long.
You sit there and act like
the mother of this nation...
But I swear I'm going to take
everything you have from you Bala.
Everything.
Both your place...
..and your husband.
Osman has upped the
security in these areas.
We have to find another
path for Lucas' army.
Karesi Bey.
What is it Karesi Bey?
Why am I seeing you again for?
We were looking for a bey whose
blood runs as wild as this river...
...but destiny made me
come across you, again.
No.
You don't come and..
..see me without a reason
Now tell me, are you trying to build...
...the bridge you couldn't
make Lucas build?
This side of this river is mine...
...and those lands are yours.
As long as you're this disrespectful...
...and rebel against your elders...
...even a bridge cannot connect us!
When I told you to unite,
you separated our ways.
You worked with the infidels
against your own blood.
That neither..
...deserves respect nor manners.
Am I working with the
infidels just because...
...I made an agreement
in terms of trade with them?
Osman Bey.
I know what you do..
...and why you do it very well.
Instead of working
with the powerful ones...
...you are screaming
everywhere that you are a Bey.
You are afraid.
I am afraid, huh?
Of you?
Of all of us. You are wandering
on all the borders in order to figure
out from where those powerful
ones are going to attack, Black Osma
You are the one coming our way.
For you keep your
enemy in your eyesight...
..it is obvious who is afraid.
Karasi Bey doesn't keep
his enemy in his eyesight.
All of them are under the ground!
But you will be always
in my eyesight, Osman.
When the time comes, you will obey me.
Then, you will be my
favorite Bey, warrior...
...and someone closer than my son.
All these wars...
...have made you go mad.
Anyone can see it since you are
attending the weddings of the infidel
We've also received your
invitation, Osman Bey.
I'll come.
I'll join the wedding of your son,
Orhan Bey. We've prepared our gift
As you commanded, I've placed
my men in Sogut, Commander Luka
We'll start the fire of the
rebellion from every corner.
Invincible Arkadeus. I knew I
didn't make a mistake by trusting you.
Is everything ready?
The weapons have been
hidden in the houses.
My men have been placed on crucial points.
We've infiltrated among the people in
such a way that even the quietest one is...
..going to find himself
in the middle of the rebellion
Good.
They'll drown in a
greater chaos in Orhan's wedding...
...than you had in
your wedding.
I'm so proud that I
have a commander like you
by my side while fighting
for Holy Rome, Arkadeus.
The victor will be ours in the end.
I'm at your side with my
all power, Commander.
There is no suspicion that the
victory will be with Byzantine.
Don't forget that you are
the torch of this rebellion.
Go now. Lead your soldiers.
KAYI TRIBE
-May it be easy.
-Thank you, Fatma Hatun.
-Thank you.
-They look great, sisters.
-Welcome.
Fatma Hatun.
Orhan Bey and Holofira Hatun
have come together finally.
Their love is legendary.
I hope the other lovers...
I'm happy for them. I hope their
happiness lasts forever, if Allah permits.
Wouldn't it be more suitable if you
congratulate Orhan Bey in person, Sarica Bey?
Are you going to keep
standing like this? Let me pass.
Sorry, Fatma Hatun. I was checking
if there is anything I could help with.
I don't know for what
reason Yusuf Bey is here.
I am here because I wish to speak
with you in person, Fatma Hatun.
Of course, if you allow
me. That's why I'm here.
What are you going to talk about?
I heard that Bala Hatun
assigned you to the warrior sisters.
We have also many
sisters who can fight, for sure.
But I'm sure your organization
will be more suitable for our army.
Well, talking about unity...
...Praise be Yusuf Bey,
you always work hard.
Right?
I will talk with my mother first.
If she sees it fit, you
can bring the hatuns
to the military camp
and we can test them.
Those who are suited to be
a member of The Sisters can be given duties.
Good, Fatma Hatun.
Fatma Hatun!
You go to the training yard.
There is little time left. They
are waiting for you for henna.
I am coming Ghazi.
Come on.
Fatma Hatun.
What do they want?
I am going to attack them with my swords!
Don't do that. I can take care of my own.
Ghazi.
Let go of me Fatma Hatun.
Ghazi come here.
Ghazi.
Ghazi Come on.
The Sisters, huh?
I know what you want Yusuf Bey.
You won't get what you want.
Here's my advice.
Don't you dare fight me in any field.
You'll lose.
You're wrong Yusuf Bey.
Look at the bride
She has henna on her hands.
Her hands so soft...
..her heart so true.
In the name of Allah.
Her door is adorned with henna.
And her form is angelic.
Bring it here my girl.
Congratulations, sweet bride.
May your home be a happy one.
Come on.
In the name of Allah.
My daughter.
My beautiful Holofira.
May Allah wish you and my Orhan
happiness in both worlds, if Allah permits.
-Ameen.
Ameen.
Fatma Hatun.
May you experience it next.
That's right.
If Allah permits, with a man that is
worthy of your bloodline and you.
Gonca.
I couldn't make it in time for the henna.
I'm sorry.
This is my wedding gift for you.
It belonged to my baby.
First, his father's
blood got spilled on it.
I didn't know then but it
was a sign for my baby.
I'll never forget that you caused this.
You also never forget.
My beautiful Holofira.
Daughter, no, no, no. Don't be upset.
Don't be sad, huh.
This is the happiest day of my life.
Come on.
KAYI TRIBE
Attention! Osman Bey!
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
My Beys who are always ready for war.
Welcome.
You have traveled from far away.
You have come from
the tribes in the borders.
I welcome you all.
-Thank you Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Come on then.
My Bey, Karesi Bey.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
You have invited us
as our younger brother.
And as your elder..
...I came to your son's wedding.
May Allah bless their marriage.
Well..
...there can't be a wedding
without Karesi Bey, right?
Thank you.
Karesi Bey.
The best...
...seat is yours.
Please take your seats.
Greek people, my brothers!
What you heard is true!
Turks killed our priest to kidnap
the bride from the wedding...
..of our commander Arcadeus!
They insulted...
...our religion and dignity!
We won't accept this!
We will take revenge
on the oppressor Turks!
They shed the blood of
our priest at our wedding!
And we will...
...burn down their wedding
with the fires of rebellion!
For The Holy Roman Empire!
For our religion!
-For our religion!
Go!
Burn down everything!
Those who...
...did this to us will
burn down with our fire!
Sergeant Aykut, should we stop them?
No, that would make things worse.
I will inform Osman Bey.
Don't let things get out of control.
As you command.
-You will pay!
-Burn everything!
Allah.
May this couple be like Adam and Hawaa...
...like Hadhrat Muhammed
(PBUH) and Mother Hatice...
...like Hadhrat Ali and Mother Fatma.
May Allah grant them love.
Ameen.
Al Fatiha.
Alright.
Congratulations.
May Allah never separate you.
If Allah permits, my Bey. Thank you.
Hold on.
Okay...
This...
...is from Osman Bey...
...and myself, my girl.
Come.
May you live long and bravely...
..like your father, if Allah permits.
Thank you Karesi Bey.
This is our gift to you.
Thank you.
Orhan.
Holofira.
Go on to the stage.
This is your Happiest day. Come on.
Go on and enjoy your dance.
Brother.
Sister.
Sister in law Gonca looks very down.
Maybe I can go speak with her.
No Fatma.
She wants to be alone.
She doesn't even want me around.
Her pain is grand...
...she even told me that we should leave.
So she's in that much pain.
It's not easy of course, losing a child...
It's not easy.
Brother.
How can you stand up tall?
A mountain would've crumbled.
A river would've flooded.
You were kept in that
cage first then lost a child.
How can you stand up tall?
Because if we show our
pain we'll crumble, Fatma.
So many enemies...
They're waiting for us to
take a stab at us in the dark.
If we fall...
...there will be a lot of people
who will stab us in the back.
Then...
...our nation would be
destroyed huh Fatma?
...that's why you hide it deep down.
You smile at everyone because of this huh?
For our nation..
...we have to risk everything.
No one will see the tears, we shed.
We'll be the strongest ones, Fatma.
They will hurt us.
They will but...
..we will never show weakness.
You're going to make me cry.
No.
My brother.
What happened?
Did you manage to charm her?
It's soon.
But we can't rush it, father.
-Lowlifes.
-Traitors.
Run.
Death to Turks.
-Traitor Turks.
-Lowlifes.
Burn it.
Revenge.
-Don't burn that.
-Kill them all.
-Please.
-Attack brothers.
For the great Byzantine.
Revenge.
Burn it.
Destroy it.
They call a good horse great...
...and a good man wild.
Come on lads, you have the field.
Come on.
What a beautiful weather.
What a great scene.
Arkadeus. Be prepared for the next step.
We've received the expected
news from Karasi Bey.
Karasi Bey has reported from
which territory our army will pass.
Osman.
While Osman is busy with rebel attacks,
we'll get back what belongs to us.
Our honor.
I'm with you until the last
drop of my blood, commander.
Karadin Castle will belong
to Byzantine once again.
We'll deal a great blow to Osman.
The ones, who thought
have beaten us, will bend
the knee against the
greatness of Holy Rome!
What did my Orhan Bey do?
He built his tent on the great lands!
What did he do to make
Holofira Hatun happy?
He broke many hordes under his sword!
Did he break any hearts?
Did he say anything bad?
He never broke hearts
or said anything bad.
He married Holofira Hatun!
Then, may Allah make them happy!
Ameen!
-Then, may Allah make them happy!
-May they live happily!
My Holofira.
My first love.
Hatun.
You've made my yesterday, today
and tomorrow happy by entering my life
My creator shall let us have babies and make
our tent a happy place, too.
I hope that we will be
always happy from now on.
My Bey.
"My Bey" huh? My Holofira.
With you...
...we have gone through a lot.
But every separation we experienced...
...made our love stronger.
In every path you set foot on...
...as long as I can...
..as long as I live..
..with all my heart..
...I will be by your side.
Oh Praise be!
My Bey.
Greek people rebelled, my Bey.
They are accusing our
shahzade of killing the priest.
Sogut is on fire.
What are you saying, Aykurt?
Our alps are trying to stop them, but...
...the rebellion is getting worse.
Sogut is on fire.
How is that possible?
If you are not powerful
enough to stop the rebellion...
...I will help you with all my state!
No!
Begum Hatun.
Go to Karadin.
Secure the castle.
As you command my Bey.
Bayhan Bey, Gencer Bey.
Take your positions in the borders.
Keep your eyes open,
and your swords sharp.
As you command my Bey.
Alaeddin.
My Bey.
Prepare the alps.
We are going to Sogut.
As you command my Bey.
What are you up to Lucas!
The army is ready for Karadin
siege, Commander Lucas!
The Turks are blinded by the rebellion.
And we will open their
eyes with Karadin siege!
My soldiers! Today...
...is the day of victory!
It's the day to save the Karadin Castle...
...stolen by the Turks!
Before Turks realize what's going on...
...we will be inside!
The victory belongs to Holy Roman Empire!
Go and show the power of
Byzantine to the whole world!
Come on!
Karadin, huh?
Sister.
Just when you were finally
going to be happy, this happened.
Gonca, let me help you.
Don't!
Stay away from me Holofira!
You brought trouble with yourself!
Enough Gonca.
Enough.
It's not the time.
Don't do it Gonca Hatun.
We're already surrounded by fire.
Holofira's upset too.
Holofira lit the fire.
She had my baby die.
And now the fire is burning Kayi.
You started the Greek riot, Holofira.
The fire you started..
...is burning the people now.
Aunt...
...Holofira's upset too, don't you see?
I see Fatma. I see it all.
But you're blind.
I guess you don't see my pain Fatma.
Maybe...
...I have no place in this tribe.
Don't be upset aunt.
Such hatred. Such anger.
They burned it all down.
They'll pay for it Bala Hatun.
They will.
How will we fix this?
They're insane. They're like rabid dogs.
How will they behave before
they see the strength of the Turks?
If wolves expressed anger always...
...they'd be just like dogs.
Orhan. Alaeddin.
You'll lead the Alps.
Increase security everywhere.
As you wish my Bey.
Let's go.
Turks and Greeks can never battle.
The Greeks that are caught will
be caught with no bloodshed.
I requested Alps from the tribe.
We'll secure the borders too.
Begum Hatun. Lukas is
at the gates with his army.
Lukas.
What will we do now sister?
Come.
Lukas.
Bithinia's ruler...
...the honorable commander
of Byzantines, Lukas...
...wants you to surrender
and hand over Karadin.
I guess Lukas' army wants to
taste my army's swords today.
If he attacks...
...that devil's army will vanish
before they get to my gates.
Don't trust yourself so much Begum Hatun.
Osman Bey or someone else...
..won't be able to come in time.
Have mercy on your brother
and your Alps. Surrender.
Karadin's people aren't afraid of Shahada.
Lukas can do as he wishes.
If the support doesn't
make it in time it will...
...be a challenge to go
against that army but...
..we'll see.
My sister in law Gonca likes you a lot.
You know that right Holofira?
Gonca and I were like sisters.
How could she think that I would hurt her?
Her heart is aflame right now.
That's why she's doing this.
Until her fire dies out...
...we have to be understanding.
Fatma.
You've grown up a lot.
Gonca is missing.
What are you saying Ulgen Hatun?
I've checked everywhere,
she's not here.
What?
She's not here Fatma. I went
to her tent and she wasn't there.
I've checked everywhere,
where could she be?
May Allah protect!
Her pain is so grand that...
...she even told me that we should leave.
Sister in law..
...don't let it be that
you did something crazy.
Cerkutay, open it.
This is not something the
innocent Greek people would do.
It's clear...
...the devil is among us.
Bad deeds are done in secret but
they never remain as such my bey.
We will of course make
those who did this pay.
We will.
From Ilbay.
From Ilbay, my bey.
What does it say my bey?
Lucas is attacking Karadin.
This is a move to make us waste time.
Cerkutay, tell the
alps to increase the security measures.
-As you wish my bey.
-We're going to Karadin right away.
Karadin.
You are the mark of my victory.
Soldiers.
Those who welcome death with bravery...
...will never be defeated.
Turks are trying to end our race.
We will never let that happen.
For great Byzantine.
Take war formation.
Archers on my mark. Everyone
in their place. Come on.
Come on alps.
May Allah be with us.
Attack.
Stop.
Attention.
Where are you...
...going all fired up like this Lucas?
What are you doing here Karesi Bey?
I came to show a commander
who thinks he's very smart...
...his place.
You...
Weren't you on my side Karesi Bey?
If I was on your side...
...would I be standing here right now?
I'm not on your side,
I'm right before you.
Don't you think I beat
whoever tries to attack
Turk's lands even if
they belong to Osman?
Karasi Bey, I'm here with my whole army.
I'm here to capture Karadin.
You cannot stop me.
If your whole army is here, who
will keep Brusa away from my wrath?
You are making a mistake, Karasi Bey.
This will lead you to your end.
I always follow the
things I believe are right.
My army is at Brusa, both on the
sea and land. They are ready in Nikea.
They are waiting for my order.
If a castle falls here, a
city will be destroyed there.
So, you are taking the
risk of being my enemy.
Its consequences will be dire, Karasi Bey.
Here is the battleground,
here is the warrior!
I never refrain from war.
You either retreat from Karadin..
...or I'll let no one be alive in Brusa!
Do you want Osman's victory?
What do you want? Why?
You don't understand, Lukas.
Osman has gotten greater loss now.
I'm Osman Bey.
I've walked a great
distance. I've run a lot.
I've found many comrades beside
me and many enemies against me
I didn't give up, I didn't give in.
I've matured in the road of
The Truth with the sunnah of the Prophet.
I was ready to sacrifice
my life and my comrades' life...
...in order to make
sure the Turks live forever.
While we were a small tribe, I've
scaled up my ideals and became a state.
Now I am saying this to the whole world!
Either victory or death!